现在我们已经将站点添加到GitHub上，
Now that we've added the site to GitHub,
让我们来看看你可以在GitHub里面做什么。
let's go around and take a look at what you can do inside of GitHub.
我们已经看了分支部分，
We've already taken a look at the branches section,
但你可以看到这里有一个完整的子菜单包含了所有类型的东西。
but you can see that you have this sort of entire sub menu here with all types of things.
除了你们的常规菜单，
In addition to your regular menu,
里面有你的账户和个人资料的工作偏好等等。
which has your sort of work preferences for your account and your profile and all that stuff.
所有这些东西都在这里
There's all these things right here.
我们来看看它们
So let's just kind of go through them.
你可以用GitHub做的一件事是查看不同的分支，
One of the things that you can do with GitHub is take a look at different branches,
我们已经看过了，你可以删除和编辑新的分支。
which we've looked at, and you can delete and edit new branches.
你几乎可以在GitHub本地做所有你能做的事情。
And you can actually do almost everything that you can do locally inside of GitHub.
所以我们可以取，例如这个自述文件，
So we can take, e.g. this readme file,
我们可以通过点击编辑它，
and we can edit it by clicking on it,
或者记住自述文件相当于你的主页。
or actually remember that the readme file is sort of your home page.
这就是这里展示的
It's what is being displayed right here.
如果我们看一下这个按钮，
So if we take a look at this button right here,
你可以看到你可以在里面编辑任何东西。
you can see that you can actually edit anything in there.
这是一种叫做markdown的特殊形式。
It's in a special format called markdown.
Markdown很简单。
Markdown is pretty simple.
这个标签率意味着我想要创造一个一级标题，
This hashtag rate here means that I want to create a headline level one,
然后你就像平常一样写出段落。
and then you just write out your paragraphs like you normally would.
它在这里有一个预览按钮你可以预览你所做的改变
It does have a preview button right here so you can preview the changes that you're making.
我们现在不打算做任何改变
We're not going to do any changes right now.
稍后我将向您展示如何执行拉取请求和创建更改
I'll show you how to do pull requests and create changes later on.
现在 我们先取消
For right now, we're going to cancel.
除了能够查看不同的代码片段，
In addition to being able to just look at your different pieces of code,
你可以添加一个文件。
you can actually add a file.
通常你只需要把文件拖到GitHub上就可以了。
And normally you can do that just by dragging a file into GitHub.
这是把东西放到github中最快的方法
So that's the quickest way of putting something in github.
但你也可以在这里做
But you can also do that through here.
你可以上传文件或创建新文件，
You can upload files or create a new file,
当你创建一个新文件时，如果你愿意，
and when you create a new file, if you want,
实际上，您可以通过先添加目录名来创建目录。
you can actually create a directory by adding the directory name first.
所以你会说，比如，下标，然后加上斜杠，
So you would say, like, sub and then put a slash,
这会为你创建一个额外的目录，然后你可以在里面放一个名字。
and that would create the additional directory for you, and then you can place a name in there.
点击取消，
So I'm going to hit cancel,
因为我不想添加任何东西。
because I don't really want to add anything.
我们继续吧 别再管这事了
Let's go ahead and leave this alone.
然后你可以添加标签
And then you can add tags.
现在，你没有任何文本，我们可以在你的项目中添加标签
Right now, you don't have any text, we can add tags into your projects
而文字只是让人们找到你的内容的方式
and the text are just ways to allow people to find your content
如果有人正在搜索你的一个项目。
if somebody is doing a search for one of your projects.
注意这里的about部分有我们项目的测试网站
So notice that over here we have the about section where it has a test website for our project.
如果你点击这里 你可以添加更多的信息
If you click right here, you'll be able to add a little bit more information.
其中一个非常有用的东西是，如果你的项目有一个网站，
One of the things that's pretty useful is that if there is a website for your project,
你可以把它加在这里。
you can add it right here.
很多时候代码仓库会是一些代码，
So a lot of times the repo will be sort of some code,
但你已经在网上发布了你的网站，
but you've actually published your website on the Web,
你可以在这里放一个链接。
so you can put a link to it right here.
主题是你如何创造方法，让人们在GitHub上找到你如果他们在做搜索。
And topics is how you create ways, again, of people finding you on GitHub if they're doing a search.
你可以在这里输入HTML 然后加一个逗号
So you can type in here, HTML, and then you add a comma.
无论何时你想添加一个新标签，css逗号和Java脚本，
Whenever you want to add a new tag, css comma and Java script, perhaps,
如果有人在找这个，
if somebody's looking for that,
然后你可以在这里输入标签，然后你也可以选择你想要显示的项目。
then you can type the tags in here, and then you can also choose what items you want to show.
所以我不打算讲发行版和包，
So I'm not really gonna be covering releases and packages,
所以我们可以把它们去掉，
so we can maybe take those out,
你可以自定义所有东西的样子。
and you can sort of customize the way that everything looks.
现在你可以看到这个短了一点，
And now you can see that this is a little bit shorter,
我们在这里有这些小标签。
and we have these little tags in here.
除此之外 还有各种子标签
So in addition to that, there's also all kinds of sub tabs.
我很快地过一遍
So I'll just go through them pretty quickly.
有些你不会用到 但有些是很重要的
You're not going to use some of these, but some of these are pretty important.
第一个是问题 问题是你如何为自己或他人写小纸条
So 1st one is issues. Issues is how you write little notes for yourself or others.
这些可以用来做项目
And these can be sort of like to do items.
你可以创建它，然后把它分配给个人，
And you can create it to do and then assign it to an individual,
然后那个人可以对你分配给他们的任务进行评论，
and then that individual can comment on the to do that you've assigned them,
这就是你开始与人合作的方式。
and it's how you start to collaborate with people.
这里还有一个非常重要的标签
There's another tab here that's pretty important
我们稍后会在实际更改文档调用拉取请求时讲到。
that we'll get into later when we actually change our document call pull requests.
拉请求是批准其他人所做更改的方法
Pull requests are ways of approving changes that somebody else has made.
你也可以用它来比较不同的分支 看看它们之间有什么不同
And you can also use this to compare different branches and take a look at what the difference is in between them.
下一个是动作。
So next up is actions.
它们可以让你做一些事情，比如运行测试或将代码自动发送到托管的地方。
They let you do things like run tests or send your code to where it will be hosted automatically.
它是一种程序，你可以写它来管理你的仓库，
It's sort of a program that you can write to manage your repositories,
他们可以做各种各样的事情。
and they can do all kinds of things.
你也可以下载或使用别人创建的动作
And you can actually also download or use actions that other people have built.
它非常方便，但有点先进，
It extremely handy, but somewhat advanced,
所以当你第一次开始的时候，这不是你想要的。
so not the thing you want to mess around with when you're 1st getting started.
项目是您可以管理正在使用的代码的地方
The project is where you can manage the code that is being used.
你可以做一个叫做可弯曲板的东西
You can create something called a can bend board.
开发人员就是这样管理他们的项目的 这样你就可以创建任务了
That is how developer manage their projects, so you can create tasks.
这有点像一种幻想，太立体了，
It's sort of like a fancy to do that is too dimensional,
有点像Excel电子表格，你可以
kind of like a Excel spreadsheet, where you can have
做一些事情 然后把它移到不同的列中
to do something then move it into different columns.
这是一个非常有趣的方式来计划你可能想要研究的项目，
It's a really fun way to plan your projects that you may want to look into,
Github也给你一个wiki。维基只是一个简单的方法
github also gives you a wiki. And the wiki is just a simple way to
创建便于人们查看的文档
create documentation that is really easy for people to look at.
它有点像创造
It sort of like creates
一个小网站 它不是很高级 所以你不需要用到wiki
like a little website. It's not very advanced, so you don't really also need the wiki.
很多文档都可以在主项目中完成，
A lot of the documentation could just be done with mark down in the main project,
或者你可以建一个网站，上面有相关文档。
or you can actually just build a website that has the documentation.
这里还有一个安全区域，
Now, there's also a section for security,
您可以在哪里管理您的安全策略
which is where you can manage your policies for security
为你的代码出现问题时的情况做好准备。
and set things up for what's gonna happen when there are problems with your code.
这是非常重要的一部分，
This is a pretty important section,
但同样，它是高级的，所以你不需要担心它作为你第一次学习GitHub本身。
but again, it's sort of advanced, so you don't need to worry about it as your 1st learning about GitHub itself.
然后是洞察部分 这很有用
Then there's this insights section. This is pretty useful.
它可以让你知道为这个项目做出贡献的不同的人
It can let you know the different people who are contributing to this project.
这是一个私人项目，
This is a private project,
因此，您将能够找到为您的应用程序工作的不同人员的贡献。
so you will be able to find the contributions of the different people that are working on your application.
还有流量问题
And then there's things like traffic.
我刚刚创建了这个，所以这里什么都没有，
I just created this so there's nothing here,
但是当人们访问这个存储库时，流量会告诉你，
but the traffic will let you know when people come to this repository,
他们在GitHub做什么。
what they're doing within GitHub.
所以它对跟踪发生的事情非常有用
So it's actually quite useful for tracking what's going on.
然后你可以看看其他的一些，
And then you can take a look at some of these other ones,
比如你提交了多少次，人们提交的频率有多高，
like how many commits you've done, how often people have submitted stuff,
然后依赖关系图会显示你的项目正在使用什么工具，等等。
and then the dependency graph will be what tools your project is using, et cetera, et cetera.
除此之外 在设置下还有很多其他的设置
So in addition to that, there are also a whole bunch of other settings under settings.
这是你可以加的地方 例如
And this is where you can add, e.g.
您可以将此存储库转换为模板
you can convert this repository to be a template.
所以当你创建一个新的存储库时，
So when you create a new repository,
你可以选择这种方式来创建一个简单的网站。
you can choose this as perhaps a way of creating a simple website.
你所需要做的就是点击模板库，
All you need to do is just click on template repository,
它会把它转换成模板。
and it will convert it into a template.
当你回到你的储存库时，
And then when you go back into your repository,
你会看到它现在是一个私有模板。
you'll see that it's as it's a private template now.
回到设置。让我们来做一下，
So back to settings. Let's go ahead and do that,
因为我们并不需要它是一个存储库。
because we don't really need it to be a repository.
这是你如何添加一个图像，当人们将url复制到你的项目时，
This is how you can add an image that when people copy the url to your project,
它会显示出这个图像。
it'll show up this image here.
然后你也可以在这部分关闭很多功能
And then you can also turn off a lot of features over here in this section.
很多其他的东西都很先进，
A lot of these other things are pretty advanced,
所以我真的不想掩盖它们。
so I don't really want to cover them.
如果你想的话 你可以点击它们
You can tap through them if you want to.
你可以看到有一个地方你可以管理它是你的默认分支，
You can see that there's the place where you can sort of manage which is your default branch,
诸如此类。
and stuff like that.
我想给你们展示的最后一件重要的事情是这里的最后一个链接率，叫做Github Pages。
The last important thing that I want to show you is this very last link rate here, called Github Pages.
因此，GitHub Pages旨在让您从GitHub存储库托管您的网站。
So GitHub Pages is designed to allow you to host your website from a gitub repository.
这是一种方法，如果你有一个像我们这样简单的静态网站，
So this is a way, if you have a simple, static site like ours,
你可以让GitHub免费托管你的网站。
you can actually have GitHub host your site for free.
所以你要做的就是选择你想要使用的分支，
So what you do is you have to choose the branch that you want to use,
你可以选择把所有的东西都放在你网站的主要层次上。
and you can choose to either have everything at the main level of your website.
而不是把所有东西都放在旧的这里，比如我有这个docs文件夹，
So instead of putting everything in a older here, like I have this docs folder,
你可以把所有的index。html放到这一层，
you can just put everything the index.HTML at this level,
然后它将从根级别构建网站。
and it will then build the website from the root level.
或者你也可以把所有东西都放在docs文件夹里，这就是为什么我把那个文件夹叫做docs，
Or you can also have everything in a docs folder, which is the reason why I call that folder docs,
因为我知道我要继续创建GitHub页面，
because I knew that I was going to go ahead and create GitHub pages,
或者使用GitHub页面来显示它。
or use GitHub pages to allow you to display it.
所以我要回到这里选择我，
So I'm going to go back to choosing me here,
然后打开docs文件夹，点击安全键。
and then I'm going to use the docs folder, and I'll hit safe.
之后，你会看到这样的URL。
And then after you do that, you should see a URL like this.
它确实需要一点时间才能在GitHub上看到它的结果。
It does take a little bit of time before you can see the result of it to GitHub.
确实需要做一些设置 但这很酷
Does have to do a little bit of set up, but this is pretty cool.
一旦运行 你就可以访问这个网站
Once it runs, you can go to this website.
现在，你的将是不同的，
Now, yours will be different,
我已经添加了一个自定义域到我的整个github帐户。
and I have added a custom domain to my entire github account.
您还可以添加自己的自定义域名。
You can also add your own custom domain.
这里有一些设置，
There is a little bit of setup,
但是你的应该稍微长一点，在最后加上存储库的名称。
but yours should be a little bit longer, with the name of the repository at the very end.
注意，因为这是一个私有存储库，
And notice that because this is a private repository,
这个站点仍然是公开的，因为您确实希望能够在任何机器上查看它。
this site will still be public, because you do want to be able to look at it on any machine.
还有一种方法是选择一种叫做Jakyl的服务，它可以让你更容易地建立网站，
And there is also a way to choose a service called Jakyl that will let you build websites a little bit easier,
但我真的很喜欢用GitHub来创建简单的网站，让他们免费托管很多网站，例如。
but I really like to use GitHub to create simple websites and let them host a lot of sites for free, e.g.
我的个人博客rebel.org都是由GitHub免费托管的，
my personal blog, rebel.org, is all hosted for free by GitHub,
我甚至不用担心会有多少流量。
and I don't even have to worry about how much traffic it gets.
他们只是对此很好
They just are very nice about it.
现在这些设置中有很多选项
So now there's so many options in all these settings.
我们有一些很棒的
We have some great
更深入这个主题的课程
courses that go deeper on this topics.
不过，我真的很喜欢GitHub免费托管东西的能力。
I do really like the ability to have GitHub host things for free, though.